iotransfer.net 2017-09-05

# Privacy

## IOTransfer Studio Privacy Policy

**Last Updated: June 28, 2017**

Your privacy is extremely important to us. To better protect your privacy, we are making this privacy policy available to you so you can learn about our online information practices and the way we collect and use your information.

### How Your Information is Collected

When you place an order from our website ("Site"), or download, activate or register a product with us, you will be prompted to provide (and we will collect) certain types of personally identifiable information, such as your name, postal address, e-mail address, telephone number, financial information (such as your credit card number) and other unique information such as user IDs and passwords, transaction information and product and service preferences. We also collect the e-mail addresses of customers who communicate with us via e-mail and those who provide their e-mail address when joining our mailing list. In addition, we collect personally identifiable information that is voluntarily provided to us by visitors to our Site in connection with activities such as contest participations, survey information and member account registrations.

We may collect aggregate (anonymous) information from all visitors to our Site, regardless of whether they place an order with us or download software, volunteer such information, communicate with us, join our mailing list or otherwise.

Some of our products may install an "Agent" on your computer or mobile device that will appear to you in the form of a Device Manager or Dashboard. This Agent may be used by the initial registrant of the product to view certain information regarding such user's device, and may also be used by such user to access certain information regarding the devices of others users of the product that have been invited to install and use the product by such initial user, under such user's license. This Agent may also collect personally identifiable information of such users that are invited to install and use the product, if such users actually place an order from our Site, or download, activate or register a product with us. This Agent may collect specific information about such device, including system specifications, programs running in real time and programs scheduled to execute upon startup of the device.

While some products may enable you to choose to invite or permit other users the right to install and use a product (if your product license provides for multiple users and/or contains an email "invite" feature), we strongly discourage the sharing of log-in information, passwords and other personal information. We are not liable for disclosure/use of any personal information or alteration of/damage to a device resulting from the sharing of such information.

We may also collect information about you from commercially available sources. Such information may include your name, address, email address and demographic data. The information that we may collect from these sources may be used along with the information that we collect from you when you visit the Site.

### Cookies and Other Information Gathering Tools

Like many sites, we use "cookies." Cookies are small text files that reside on your device and identify you as a unique user. Cookies allow us to, among other things, measure activity on our Site and personalize your experience. For example, cookies enable us to remember your viewing preferences without requiring you to re-type a user name and password. Cookies also allow us to track your status or progress when ordering products from us. If you choose, you can set your browser to reject cookies or you can manually delete individual or all of the cookies on your device by following your browser's help file directions. However, if you reject or delete cookies you may have some trouble accessing and using some of the pages and features on our Site. We also use other common information gathering tools such as web beacons and embedded web links.

We also make use of log files in order to track information such as internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), platform type and date/time stamps. Included in the log files, we gather information that can be used in trend analysis, administration of the site, and overall demography tracking; this information is gathered through the counting of clicks and not linked to personally identifiable information.

### Children's Information

We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of 18 and we do not target our Site to children under the age of 18.

### How We Use Your Information

We use your personally identifiable information to fulfill purchases that you make through our Site, for marketing purposes, to provide service and support, and to improve the quality and type of applications we make available via our products. We share the information with other reputable organizations for service, support and marketing purposes.

If you provide us with your postal or e-mail address, you may receive periodic mailings from us with information about products, services and upcoming events. We may share your information with select business partners so that they may offer products and services that we believe will be attractive to our customers and to those who have subscribed to our mailing list.

In addition, we may share your information with third parties in order to: (i) respond to the requests of police and governmental authorities, (ii) comply with any law, regulation, subpoena, or court order, (iii) help prevent fraud or to enforce or protect our rights or (iv) protect the personal safety of our employees and third parties. We may also share your information with third parties for business reasons, such as in the context of the sale or merger of our company or business.

Aggregate, anonymous data collected is statistical in nature, and does not include personally identifiable information. This data may be used to improve your user experience and the overall quality of our services.

When you provide us with your credit card information we may redirect that information to certain third parties only for the purpose of payment processing in accordance with their own privacy and security policies.

### Third Party Ad Servers

We may use third-party service providers to serve ads on our behalf on this Site. Such providers may collect anonymous information about your visits to our Site. They may use information about your visits to this Site to target advertisements for goods and services. This anonymous information is collected through the use of a pixel tag, which is industry standard technology used by many major websites. No personally identifiable information is collected or used in this process (such as your name, phone number or postal or email address).

We also work with third parties to monitor certain pages of our Site for the purpose of reporting website traffic and other advertising statistics. These third parties may use cookies and/or other monitoring technologies to compile anonymous statistics about our Site visitors. However, no personally identifiable information is transferred to these third parties.

### Links to Third Party Websites

The Site may contain links to third-party websites for your convenience and information. We do not control those websites or make any representations or warranties about their use or the third party policies that govern such use. Any personal information that is obtained by third parties is not covered by this privacy policy. We encourage you to review the privacy policies of third-party websites.

### Security

We maintain reasonable and appropriate security procedures, but we cannot guarantee that your information will be secure in every circumstance.

### Notices

If we are required to provide you with notice of a particular event or incident, we will send you such notice by mail, email or telephone.

### Notification of Changes

We may revise this Privacy Policy from time to time. If we decide to change our Privacy Policy, we will post the revised policy here. As we may make changes at any time without notifying you, we suggest that you periodically consult this Privacy Policy.
